<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Ananke</title>
    <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Ananke</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chaparral Seed Bank Project</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/seed_bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/seed_bank/</guid>
      <description>Description of project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GCC Native Plant Nursery Project</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/gcc_npn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/gcc_npn/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this project is to determine the feasibility of a native plant nursery in Gaviota, at Baron Ranch or elsewhere. A new native plant nursery would increase the supply of native plants regionally and directly supply restoration projects and native landscaping efforts. This nursery will also provide opportunities for community involvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Conservation Planning for the Gaviota Region</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/endangermond_gp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/endangermond_gp/</guid>
      <description>This project is a Bren Group Project through the Bren School of Environmental Science &amp;amp; Management at UC Santa Barbara. Our client for this project is The Nature Conservancy, and the project members are Alexandra Martin, Alissa Patterson, Alessandra Puig-Santana, Katherine Rosencrance, Pol Carbó Mestre, and myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agricultural Abandonment</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/sparcl_ag_abandonment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/sparcl_ag_abandonment/</guid>
      <description>This project is through emLab (UCSB) and Conservation International, through a larger project called SPARCL (Spatial Planning for Climate Change: Land Use for Conservation, Agriculture, and Energy)
A study analyzing changes in agricultural abandonment under a variety of projected climate scenarios, its impacts on connectivity, and how future agricultural demand can be satisfied with these abandoned lands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
